<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<BMT_BiomesPrehistoric>Biomes! Prehistoric</BMT_BiomesPrehistoric>
	
	<BMT_PrehistoricSettingsDesc>You can change your settings at any time, including mid-game. It will affect plant/animal spawns after you change it, but not anything that's already spawned.\n\nSettings will only apply to supported biomes. If your favorite biome isn't patched yet, tell us on Steam or on Discord!</BMT_PrehistoricSettingsDesc>
	
	<BMT_DinoAndVanillaLabel>Animals Only</BMT_DinoAndVanillaLabel>
	<BMT_DinoAndVanillaDesc>Prehistoric animals will spawn but prehistoric plants will not. They will spawn alongside both vanilla and modded plants and animals.</BMT_DinoAndVanillaDesc>
	
	<BMT_DinoAndPlantLabel>Animals and Plants</BMT_DinoAndPlantLabel>
	<BMT_DinoAndPlantDesc>Adds prehistoric animals and plants to your game. They will spawn like any others in a biome.</BMT_DinoAndPlantDesc>
	
	<BMT_DinoWorldLabel>Prehistoric World</BMT_DinoWorldLabel>
	<BMT_DinoWorldDesc>A complete overhaul to your world: Only prehistoric animals and plants can spawn wild or be sold by traders.</BMT_DinoWorldDesc>

	<BMT_PrehistoricAnimalCommonality>Prehistoric Animal Commonality: {0}%</BMT_PrehistoricAnimalCommonality>
	<BMT_PrehistoricAnimalCommonalityTooltip>Changes how common wild prehistoric animals are when compared to other animals. By default they are as common as other animals. Values below 100% will make prehistoric animals less common, while values above it will make them appear more frequently.</BMT_PrehistoricAnimalCommonalityTooltip>

	<BMT_PrehistoricPlantCommonality>Prehistoric Plant Commonality: {0}%</BMT_PrehistoricPlantCommonality>
	<BMT_PrehistoricPlantCommonalityTooltip>Changes how common wild prehistoric plants are when compared to other plants. By default they are as common as other plants. Values below 100% will make prehistoric plants less common, while values above it will make them appear more frequently.</BMT_PrehistoricPlantCommonalityTooltip>

	<BMT_Select>Select</BMT_Select>

	<BMT_NestAlert>{0_indefinite} has angered nearby dinosaurs by getting too close to their nests!</BMT_NestAlert>
	
	<BMT_LetterLabelSaurumboPasses>Rare saurumbos</BMT_LetterLabelSaurumboPasses>
	<BMT_LetterSaurumboPasses>A small herd of saurumbos have wandered into the area.\n\nPeaceful by nature, these rare creatures are extremely dangerous when confronted. Some traders are willing to pay a lot of money for their precious razor feather.\n\nSaurumbos will leave the area in a few days.</BMT_LetterSaurumboPasses>
  
	
	
</LanguageData>