<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ModMetaData>

    <name>Biomes! Prehistoric</name>
    <author>The Biomes Mod Team</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.3</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <packageId>BiomesTeam.BiomesPrehistoric</packageId>
    <modDependencies>
        <li> 
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>BiomesTeam.BiomesCore</packageId>
            <displayName>Biomes! Core</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2038000893</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
        <li>BiomesTeam.Core</li>
        <li>BiomesTeam.BiomesIslands</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <description>
Dinos, Synapsids, and Pterosaurs oh my!

Step into the future, to a time where you'd never expect to find dinosaurs and yet have found them abundant!
Gone are the modern animals and plants, replaced with infinitely cooler prehistoric beasts!
From Dimetrodon to Carnotaurus, your game has never been more dinoey.


Biome! Prehistoric brings to life a multitude of prehistoric animals as well as plants, with the eventual goal of allowing players to experience Rimworld purely with prehistoric life. With over 50 different species of prehistoric creature, we fill each and every biome with new animals, even more with Biomes! Islands!

While realism is the general goal for much of the creature art in this mod, some small liberties are taken for the sake of the "Rule of cool."

The rapid and unexpected re-terraforming of the rimworld was nearly catastrophic for its various humanoid denizens, but its aftermath came with even more surprises. Gone were the majority of the species to which they had grown accustomed, instead they came to soon encounter many new species that had been extinct for many millennia back on Earth, brought back to life by the will and whim of an unfathomable Archotech. 
    </description>
    
</ModMetaData>
